apocalypse ain't
over stay out of trouble Nana as long as
you get into
plenty yes
ma'am say bacon One More Time bacon one
more
time if it isn't my favorite piggy pal
been up to no good lately I'm not your
pal we how about swine s
my ham slice
[Music]
porcupyne takes all kinds to make a
world blah blah
blah Isn't it Reckless to pull enemies
toward
us afraid he getting too close nope just
thinking of the team it would help if
you did
too roadhog take them head on go hey I
want a mission too try not to blow
yourself up a but it's me
specialty so I'm trying to ask everybody
this what is your favorite animal watcha
Mari uh yeah I can see
it I remember OverWatch tailing you back
in the day before you teamed up with
your
Sidekick quieter
times I saw you at caleris they let you
in there well I guess no one was going
to stop
you get a big payout for scrapping you H
you may certainly try think I won't I
think you
can't hey big man you got any requests a
little silence would be
nice I hate it here then you can hit it
anywhere you got a problem junker I
don't do problems just
Solutions
yeah how are the rates for Mercenaries
down there
modest no one pays what we're
worth cute ma cute
hook follow my lead and we make it out
of here in one piece watch The High
Ground huh I didn't take you for a
tactician you're used to
it I like your
mask I said I like your mask dude
okay those who seek only to enrich
themselves live the most impoverished
lives of
all yeah and those who seek my wrath
tend to find it that's why I'm an
artist are you breathing petrol or
something more interesting what some no
thank you I'll just
observe moo the Wreckers want you back
thought you might like to
know they'll hate that I'll pass it
along you stole a lot of things that
Helix was supposed to protect what's it
to you my unit would have eaten you
alive are you sure that gas you inhale
is safe it tastes
good I think I added too much base to my
new
track no such thing